from CNBC TV18 about the block deal in ICI Lombard that
ICICI Bank, the
promoter entity, has bought it, and
Bhartiya Enterprises, which owned it, has
sold it. It's a good move.
It's considered a clean-out trade right now.
Normally, stocks outperform after a clean-out trade,
and that's probably what's happening here as well. Right now,
look at ICICI Lombard. The trend in GI
is definitely positive. This is a
breakout of a flag pattern, with targets around 1745. I think
you could see an up move of 50% from the current level.
You can still buy at the current level.
Place stop losses below 1669.
Okay, so right now, it's ICICI Lombard or
ICI GI. Now, let's do one thing:
address today's Stocks of the Day
and go to Sumit first. But
before that, let's talk about Havells, which is today
's Stock of the Day.  This is the day, why did this move happen?
Sumit. Good morning. Today,
a good move is seen coming for Havells due to the report of Golden Sachs.
Coleman Sachs has
released a report and has upgraded Havells.
Along with the upgrade, the target seems to be
around ₹1.60.
They have
talked about multiple tailwinds. First, the
company is on the path of growth revival with a good leadership and a
good distribution growth. It
seems that from here a good
upside will be seen opening up because the
recent cost cutting done by the company will provide
some support to the margins of the company
and they will
also be seen coming within the going forward numbers. Plus, there has been
some easing out of their costs due to outsourcing in front of their own manufacturing, so that will
also be good for the company.
This company is continuously spending on its brands and has
added new capacity recently.
She is also working for the company in Rajasthan
and talks of double digit
revenue growth are being
expected in Q4. Along with this,
Lloyds had given
a very strong number in the last quarter, so there
too an improvement is
seen coming continuously on the margin front. In this
context, a buy report is being done on Havells
with a target of 1600 to 1660.
And what are today's stocks of the day,
if we look at the remaining stocks apart from Havells, the
first name that comes is of Andhra Cement
where there is talk of selling a part from some promoters
and there is
talk of selling a part around 5 rupees. However, the
initial impact on this stock is
negative around 4 rupees. The
floor price is around 90, that is,
this price was kept at a discount of around 19 to 20 rupees from yesterday's closing. Its
impact is visible here.
CMS Info where there is a discount of around 19 to 20 rupees.
A block happened around 28 in the morning and that was a
block of around 45 crore shares and a
block deal of around ₹1.41 crore was
seen taking place. CNBC Awas had already
mentioned and now their news is
confirmed here. Earlier it was above 2 but now it is
seen reaching the red mark
and Jari Agro, where the company has sold one of its
land, the impact of selling that land was there, a
rise of around 5 is being seen in the stock here in the
initial trading.
They have signed an agreement with Avari Infinity, there is
land worth around 80 crores
which they are selling in Goa and its
impact is visible in the stock. A
rise of around 5 is being seen here.
Thank you, thank you Sumit for all this
information and please bring it to the Jari screen
once and let's see its behavior today. It will
bring it up to around ₹231 level once
and yes 231 90 and  You should understand this level that at
this time, in the
last five to seven sessions,
since February 19, it almost
revisited the highs of all the sessions till now.
After that, there was a slight sinking and on
average Nifty was up by about 20 points. But if you
compare the 10 day expo with today's low,
it has maintained a fairly decent differential.
Some PSUs are moving.
I had mentioned PNB, it is moving a
little. Bank of Baroda is
generating a little swing at this time.
Let's check what SBI is doing.
SBI was sinking in the morning, but as of
now, if you look at SBI, it is almost at
761. Yes, it is a good reaction. I mean, it is
traveling above yesterday's body.
Here is a small view of yours:
see consolidation is visible on SBI for quite some time.
If you look at the last seven to eight sessions, the
stock has support around 750 at the lower level. On the
upside, there is resistance around 775.
But if  If we talk about the undertone, it
is definitely bullish, so if you have a long position, then
stay in your position with a stop loss of 749. However, the fresh buying advice will be
on the breakout. If it crosses 766, then
buy there because in this the
stock can test the level of ₹. Please note
that the views given on Money Control are the
personal views of the experts. The
website or the management is not responsible for it.
Money Control advises the users to seek the
advice of a certified expert before taking any investment decision.